{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Comics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20one%20of%20these%20superhero%20teams%20appears%20in%20the%20Invincible%20comics%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Guardians%20of%20the%20Globe",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Avengers",
        "Justice%20League",
        "Teenage%20Mutant%20Ninja%20Turtles"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20molecular%20formula%20of%20the%20active%20component%20of%20chili%20peppers%28Capsaicin%29%3F",
      "correct_answer": "C18H27NO3",
      "incorrect_answers": ["C21H23NO3", "C6H4Cl2", "C13H25NO4"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Manchester%20United%20won%20the%202013-14%20English%20Premier%20League.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20was%20the%20%231%20selling%20game%20on%20Steam%20by%20revenue%20in%202016%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Sid%20Meier%27s%20Civilization%20VI",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Grand%20Theft%20Auto%20V",
        "Counter%20Strike%3A%20Global%20Offensive",
        "Dark%20Souls%20III"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In%20Heroes%20of%20the%20Storm%2C%20the%20Cursed%20Hollow%20map%20gimmick%20requires%20players%20to%20kill%20the%20undead%20to%20curse%20the%20enemy%20team.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Books",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "In%20%22Little%20Women%22%2C%20which%20of%20the%20March%20sisters%20married%20Laurie%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Amy",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Beth", "Jo", "Meg"]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Toussaint%20Louverture%20led%20a%20successful%20slave%20revolt%20in%20which%20country%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Haiti",
      "incorrect_answers": ["France", "Cuba", "United%20States"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "How%20does%20the%20character%20Dragowizard%2C%20Qinus%20Axia%27s%20from%20the%20anime%20%22Buddyfight%22%20differ%20between%20the%20Japanese%20and%20English%20dubs%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Different%20Gender",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Different%20Body%20Proportions",
        "Different%20Backstory",
        "Different%20Appearance"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20animated%20movie%20was%20first%20to%20feature%20a%20celebrity%20as%20a%20voice%20actor%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Aladdin",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Toy%20Story",
        "James%20and%20the%20Giant%20Peach",
        "The%20Hunchback%20of%20Notre%20Dame"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20final%20game%20of%20the%20%22Zero%20Escape%22%20series%20called%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Zero%20Escape%20Zero%20Time%20Dilemma%20",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Nine%20Hours%2C%20Nine%20Persons%2C%20Nine%20Doors%20",
        "Zero%20Escape%20Virtue%27s%20Last%20Reward",
        "The%20Nonary%20Game%3A%20Sigma%27s%20Last%20Life"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Vehicles",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20UK%20Train%20does%20NOT%20go%20over%20125MPH%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Sprinter",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Class%2043", "Javelin", "Pendolino"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mythology",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20is%20NOT%20a%20god%20in%20Norse%20Mythology.",
      "correct_answer": "Jens",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Loki", "Tyr", "Snotra"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Vehicles",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The%20General%20Motors%20EV1%20was%20the%20first%20street-legal%20production%20electric%20vehicle.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20of%20these%20country%27s%20capitals%20starts%20with%20the%20letter%20B%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Lebanon",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Jordan", "Kuwait", "Qatar"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20of%20these%20songs%20is%20NOT%20in%20The%20Beatles%27%20album%20%22Sgt.%20Pepper%27s%20Lonely%20Hearts%20Club%20Band%22%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Strawberry%20Fields%20Forever",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Getting%20Better",
        "Fixing%20a%20Hole",
        "Lucy%20in%20the%20Sky%20with%20Diamonds"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science%20%26%20Nature",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20is%20considered%20classical%20conditioning%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Pavlov%27s%20dog%20experiments",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Skinner%20box%20experiment",
        "Schr%C3%B6dinger%27s%20cat%20experiment",
        "Harlow%E2%80%99s%20monkey%20experiments"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "In%20the%20movie%20%22Back%20to%20the%20Future%2C%22%20what%20speed%20does%20Doc%20Brown%27s%20DeLorean%20need%20to%20reach%20in%20order%20to%20travel%20through%20time%3F",
      "correct_answer": "88%20mph",
      "incorrect_answers": ["77%20mph", "100%20mph", "70%20mph"]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20of%20these%20covert%20groups%20employs%20Sam%20Fisher%20to%20work%20as%20a%20Splinter%20Cell%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Third%20Echelon",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Voron", "Black%20Arrow", "The%20Engineers"]
    }
  ]
}
